<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Articles on Danny Freese - Coding for a Living</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/</link><description>Recent content in Articles on Danny Freese - Coding for a Living</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Openshift Security Best References</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/openshift/fav-ocp-security-posts/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/openshift/fav-ocp-security-posts/</guid><description>OpenShift is marketed at the enterprise ready flavor of Kuberentes, with all the support of Red Hat and the high quality out of the gate security offered on the platform.
That doesn&amp;rsquo;t make Security on OpenShift any less confusing. There are Security Context, Pod Security Context, RBAC. When and why should you leverage RBAC and SCCS. Here are the list of my favorite blogs that I like to refer to when I need a quick reminder or a quick fix for demo.</description></item><item><title>Understanding Envoy Proxy</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/understanding-envoy-proxy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/understanding-envoy-proxy/</guid><description>At this point Service Mesh related techologies have been on the rise since around 2017 and many of us are familiar with the solutions out there: Istio, Linkerd, Kong Mesh. Many of the existing service mesh technologies are built on top of Envoy Proxy (certainly not all of them are but many are built on Enovy) which was originally designed to support mesh-like architectures.
Well, Kong Mesh was the first mesh I had used that exposed the ablity to actually configure the Envoy Proxy sidecar - with the Proxy Template.</description></item><item><title>Women in Tech - Eff the Unconcious Bias</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/women-in-tech/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/women-in-tech/</guid><description>When I started to study computer science and make the transition into the field it was extremely glamorized from where I was standing. Oh cool I&amp;rsquo;m going to be a coder, and solve problems. Which don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, it&amp;rsquo;s completely valid and true. On top of that, there is also this talk of fighing the &amp;ldquo;uncious bias&amp;rdquo;, and if it is exists. Then all of the sudden I would look up from my desk or office and realize hmm yeah there are in fact no women in sight.</description></item></channel></rss>