<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>djfreese on Danny Freese - Coding for a Living</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/author/djfreese/</link><description>Recent content in djfreese on Danny Freese - Coding for a Living</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/author/djfreese/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ansible - How to Wait for on a Kubernetes Service with the Kubernetes Core Collection</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/code/ansible/kube-services/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/code/ansible/kube-services/</guid><description>I recently got stuck trying to figure out how to wait for a Kuberentes Services - this post will cover how I handled it with the Kuberentes Core Ansible Collection.</description></item><item><title>Book List of 2022 - A recap of the books read</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/books/year-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/books/year-2022/</guid><description>Alas I&amp;rsquo;ll admit that I probably get through approximately 1 or 2 books a month and honestly this year we had our second kid so it seems I didn&amp;rsquo;t even make it that far! So with work-life (children, exercise, children again) balance I try to make sure my time reading really counts. Which I&amp;rsquo;ve learned it really hard to do, child no. 1 is usually trying to fight me for the reading spot, and baby no.</description></item><item><title>Openshift Security Best References</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/openshift/fav-ocp-security-posts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/openshift/fav-ocp-security-posts/</guid><description>OpenShift is marketed at the enterprise ready flavor of Kuberentes, with all the support of Red Hat and the high quality out of the gate security offered on the platform.
That doesn&amp;rsquo;t make Security on OpenShift any less confusing. There are Security Context, Pod Security Context, RBAC. When and why should you leverage RBAC and SCCS. Here are the list of my favorite blogs that I like to refer to when I need a quick reminder or a quick fix for demo.</description></item><item><title>How to Write an Ansible Module Unit Test in the Ansible Collection Paradigm</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/code/ansible/module-unit-tests-mac/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/code/ansible/module-unit-tests-mac/</guid><description>This tutorial will cover two major issues. &lt;strong>One&lt;/strong> - how to setup your local workstation to build and test an ansible collection, and &lt;strong>two&lt;/strong> - resolving a mac error related to cgroups. We will finish with a helloworld unit test to validate.</description></item><item><title>What Is Spiffe and How is it used in Kuma Mesh</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-mesh-what-is-spiffe/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-mesh-what-is-spiffe/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Situation:&lt;/strong> One of the first features everyone wants from a Service Mesh is to take advantage of the &lt;code>Zero Trust / mTLS&lt;/code> that comes right out of the box. When you start to wondering into how this is all feasible in the world of workloads dynamically being created, destroyed, autoscaling the question becomes how does it all work?</description></item><item><title>Kong Mesh - Understanding how Kong Mesh translates TrafficRoute Policies to Envoy Proxy Configuration</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-filterchains/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-filterchains/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Situation:&lt;/strong> Learning more about Kong Mesh and Envoy Proxy: I wanted to understand specifically how a Traffic Route translates to Envoy Proxy Configuration and which Sidecar Proxies.</description></item><item><title>Kong Mesh - Tracing the Envoy Proxy Configuration</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-dive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-dive/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Situation:&lt;/strong> Learning more about Kong Mesh and Envoy Proxy, I wanted to be able to understand how Envoy Proxy connects all the networks dots through its configuration file. So I spun Kong Mesh with several dataplanes trace it all.</description></item><item><title>Ansible - How to Install Docker and Connect to the Docker Daemon Immediately</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/code/ansible/ubuntu-docker/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/code/ansible/ubuntu-docker/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Situation:&lt;/strong> I need to install docker and then the user immediately be able to reach the docker daemon all in the same playbook.</description></item><item><title>Resources for Understanding Envoy Proxy</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/understanding-envoy-proxy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/understanding-envoy-proxy/</guid><description>At this point Service Mesh related techologies have been on the rise since around 2017 and many of us are familiar with the solutions out there: Istio, Linkerd, Kong Mesh. Many of the existing service mesh technologies are built on top of Envoy Proxy (certainly not all of them are but many are built on Enovy) which was originally designed to support mesh-like architectures.
Well, Kong Mesh was the first mesh I had used that exposed the ablity to actually configure the Envoy Proxy sidecar - with the Proxy Template.</description></item><item><title>Women in Tech - Eff the Unconcious Bias</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/women-in-tech/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/women-in-tech/</guid><description>When I started to study computer science and make the transition into the field it was extremely glamorized from where I was standing. Oh cool I&amp;rsquo;m going to be a coder, and solve problems. Which don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, it&amp;rsquo;s completely valid and true. On top of that, there is also this talk of fighing the &amp;ldquo;uncious bias&amp;rdquo;, and if it is exists. Then all of the sudden I would look up from my desk or office and realize hmm yeah there are in fact no women in sight.</description></item></channel></rss>