<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kong Mesh on Danny Freese - Coding for a Living</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/tags/kong-mesh/</link><description>Recent content in Kong Mesh on Danny Freese - Coding for a Living</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/tags/kong-mesh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kong Mesh - Understanding how Kong Mesh translates TrafficRoute Policies to Envoy Proxy Configuration</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-filterchains/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-filterchains/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Situation:&lt;/strong> Learning more about Kong Mesh and Envoy Proxy: I wanted to understand specifically how a Traffic Route translates to Envoy Proxy Configuration and which Sidecar Proxies.</description></item><item><title>Kong Mesh - Tracing the Envoy Proxy Configuration</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-dive/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/kuma-envoy-proxy-dive/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Situation:&lt;/strong> Learning more about Kong Mesh and Envoy Proxy, I wanted to be able to understand how Envoy Proxy connects all the networks dots through its configuration file. So I spun Kong Mesh with several dataplanes trace it all.</description></item><item><title>Resources for Understanding Envoy Proxy</title><link>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/understanding-envoy-proxy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://DaniellaFreese.github.io/article/mesh/understanding-envoy-proxy/</guid><description>At this point Service Mesh related techologies have been on the rise since around 2017 and many of us are familiar with the solutions out there: Istio, Linkerd, Kong Mesh. Many of the existing service mesh technologies are built on top of Envoy Proxy (certainly not all of them are but many are built on Enovy) which was originally designed to support mesh-like architectures.
Well, Kong Mesh was the first mesh I had used that exposed the ablity to actually configure the Envoy Proxy sidecar - with the Proxy Template.</description></item></channel></rss>